本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
哇哈哈 触点得分
Ah. Ha ha! Extra point.
哥打趴了刘翔 哥比姚明强
Put some over there. Store some over there.
喂喂喂 少得意
- Hey hey hey, you know what?
咋了
What?
黄牌 黄牌警告 你过激庆贺了
Flag on the play. Flag on the play. Excessive celebration.
注：足球赛中队员庆祝进球不可过于激情，如脱衣等
纸球判罚里可没有这条规则
There's no penalties in paper football.
本来就该罚 你真雷死人了
There should be 'cause that was really annoying.
等下 你觉得哪样太雷人 是这样吗
Wait, hold on. Which point was annoying? This right here?
你不喜欢啊 要不我稍微放慢动作好了
You didn't like that? What if I slow it down for you?
-这样如何啊 -不行
- You like that? - No.
- 不喜欢吗 - 不行 还是雷
- You don't like that? - No, still annoying.
加快 加快速度
Speed it up. Speed it up!
你们俩小子在干啥啊？
What are you guys doing?
我们在玩纸板足球
We're playing paper football.
哦，纸板足球啊
Oh, paper football.
真是出色的话题啊 我来试试
Excellent topic. Okay.
纸板足球是一项美国传统竞技项目
Paper football is an american tradition.
男子们不需要任何其他道具
Allowing boys to entertain themselves with nothing more.
只要一张纸和一个水平台子就可以进行
Than a piece of paper and a flat surface.
说啥呢
What?
另一方面而言
On the other hand,
纸板足球也不需任何运动技巧和谋略
Paper football requires no athletic ability and no thinking,
故其完全是在浪费时间和纸张
Therefore making it a complete waste of time...And paper.
等下 你瞎念叨啥呢
Wait, what are you doing?
我加入了辩论队
I'm on the debate team.
我得练习为任何事辩论 不管那事有多蠢
I have to prepared to argue any topic, no matter how stupid.
那么你们俩还有什么想做的事没
So what else do you guys like to do?
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
就在这里  我们的家
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
■
校订： 山鹰逢羽
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
■
后期： Johnny-Z line
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第十八集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E18  Charlie in Charge
PJ 你怎么还在家啊
P.J., what are you doing here?
你应该去看牙医的
You're supposed to be at the dentist.
完全忘记了 你怎么不提醒我啊
Totally forgot. Why didn't you remind me?
我已经提醒过你了
I did remind you.
我在你枕边贴了条儿 给你发了简讯还有
I put a note on your pillow, I texted you and...
老妈 你已经尽力了
Mom, you did everything you could.
没有人会怪你的
No one's blaming you here.
儿子啊 你都十七岁了
P.J., honey, you are 17 years old.
到底什么时候才能不再怕牙医啊
When are you gonna stop being afraid of the dentist?
除非他不再带着那些可怕的针筒出现
When he stops coming at me with those pointy tools.
再说 我的牙现在感觉好多了
Besides, my tooth is feeling a lot better.
真的么？
Oh, really?
真的呀
Yeah.
那好 等一下
Okay, hang on one sec.
好了 给我咬这苹果
Yeah, bite it.
没问题
Sure.
好吃
Mmm!
唔唔 真美味
Mmm, delicious.
行了吧
Now...
恕我失陪了
If you'll excuse me.
哎哟哟
Ow!
你居然想让我穿着草裙秀给全班人看
You want me to wear a grass skirt. In front of the whole class?
阿乔啊 你还得套上全部行头才行
Jo, you need to put on the entire costume.
盖比 我告诉你怎么着吧
Gabe, let me explain something to you:
你就是个大白痴
You're an idiot.
你才是白痴 傻瓜
You're an idiot, idiot!
白痴
Idiot!
傻瓜
白痴
Idiot!
喂
Whoa!
哟喂 吵什么吵
Ho! What is going on in here?
阿乔和我被分到一组做这个蠢功课
Jo and I have to do this stupid project together
题目是介绍美国一个州
on one of the states.
我们不幸分到了夏威夷
We got hawaii.
是所有州里面最无趣的一个
The most boring of all the states.
就是啊
I know.
为什么我们这么倒霉 分不到好玩的州呢
Why couldn't we have gotten one of the cool states.
注：美国中部农业州，以前是大片荒野，无特色
比如内布拉斯加州啊
Like nebraska?
要是做那个题目我可有好创意呢
I had a great idea for that one.
我猜猜看啊 是不是要打扮成一个玉米杆子
Let me guess: Dress up like a corn-stalk?
才怪
No.
行了 就算夏威夷没有内布拉斯加那么有吸引力
All right, look, it may not be as glamorous as nebraska,
可是要知道 夏威夷也是一个很给力的州啊
But you know what? Hawaii's a pretty cool state.
你倒说说看有啥给力的
Name one cool thing about it.
嗯 那可是唯一的全是由岛屿组成的州啊
Well, it's the only state made up entirely of islands.
不够劲爆哦
Okay.
那它还有很多独特的动植物种群呀
It has lots of unique flora and fauna.
老爸 写报告不是罗列枯燥资料就可以的
Dad, we can't just fill up our report with a bunch of facts.
那好 知道不
All right, you know what?
夏威夷还有活火山呢
Hawaii's got an active volcano.
哎呀对 我们可以造一个火山
Hey, we could build a volcano.
人家就爱玩大爆发
I like things that explode.
不晓得哎 听起来够累人的
I don't know. Sounds like a lot of work.
那好 我也有别的主意
Okay, well, I do have another idea.
还是玩火山吧
Volcano it is.
PJ 你知道我刚才在想什么吗
P.J., you know what I was just thinking about?
记不记得以前我们都会过"妈妈和PJ"日啊
Remember when we used to have a mommy-and-p.J. Day?
我们可以再来玩一次
We should do that again.
从我七岁起就没那么玩过了吧
We haven't done that since I was seven.
就明天吧 可以随你怎么玩
How about tomorrow? We'll do whatever you want.
那你知怎样算好玩吗？
You know what'd be fun?
就是不要再玩什么"PJ和妈妈"日了
Not having a p.J.-And-mommy day.
老妈伤透了心哟
That makes mommy sad.
妈妈 我可以陪你玩的呀
Mom, I'll hang out with you if you want.
我们可以过一次"妈妈和泰迪"日
We can have a mommy-and-teddy day.
是哟 可老妈不喜欢玩那个
Yeah, mommy doesn't want that.
得了哈 就明天放学后
Okay, ah! Tomorrow after school,
我们要一起过"PJ和妈妈"日
We are having a p.J.-And-mommy day.
你一定会喜欢的
And you are gonna love it.
妈 你可以强迫我去 可不能强迫我喜欢
Mom, you can make me go, but you can't make me love it.
好吧 我喜欢总行了吧
Okay, I'll love it.
我还以为过"妈妈和泰迪"日应该很有趣
I thought mommy-and-teddy day would be fun,
显然你不这么想
But apparently not.
亲爱的 其实那个是 "PJ和牙医" 日
Honey, it's actually p.J.-And-dentist day.
哇 真狡猾
Oh, sneaky.
我唯一让他去的方法就是哄骗他
The only way for me to get him there is for me to trick him.
那这条"带盖比去玩激光大战"是什么意思
So what's this "take gabe to laser tag"?
是要带他剪头发
Haircut.
这是什么
What's this?
我刚清理我的抽屉来着
I was cleaning out my desk drawer,
翻出了一张温泉一日游的礼券
Came across this gift certificate to a day spa.
我猜是忘记送给你了 可能是情人节礼物
I think I forgot to give it to you, like, on valentine's day.
或是其他什么日子的 我不记得了
Or something. I don't know.
老爸 那魔法抽屉里有没有给我的好东西啊
Dad, was there anything for me in the magic drawer?
啊 有的
Uh, yes...
一张你四年级参加 "音乐之声"演出的传单
A flyer to your fourth-grade production of "the sound of music."
我很期待出席参观呢
I look forward to attending.
老公啊 这张礼券明天就过期了
Bob honey, this gift certificate expires tomorrow.
那我们就明天去呗
- Well, let's go tomorrow.
不行啊
I can't.
我得带PJ去看牙医
I have to take p.J. To the dentist.
妈妈 你去桑拿 我可以让PJ去牙医那
Mom, go. I'll get p.J. To the dentist.
你要怎么让他去啊
How you gonna do that?
总有法子的
I'll figure something out.
不晓得你们发现没 我可是比他聪明多
I don't know if you've noticed, but I'm smarter than him.
那查莉和盖比呢
What about charlie and gabe?
喔 他们也比大哥聪明啦
Yeah, they're smarter than him too.
这火山看来真不错 爸爸
Volcano's looking great, dad.
你觉得做的够大了吗
Do you think it's big enough?
好主意 再做大点 老爸
Good point. Little bigger, dad.
现在只是个架子
This is just the frame.
外面糊好纸以后会变的大很多了
It's gonna be a whole lot bigger. After it's been papier-mached.
不用讲详情了 做好它就是
You don't have to tell us. Just do it.
盖比 这是我家
Gabe, this is my house.
我可不需要听你或其他人的命令
I don't take orders from you or anybody else.
老公 出发去泡温泉
Bob, time to go to the spa.
马上来 亲爱的
Coming, honey.
好了 孩子们听好了
Okay, kids, let's listen up.
你们只要一按这个按钮 火山就会爆发
Now the volcano is going to erupt when you press this button.
要是你们想让它再爆发的话
If you wanted it to erupt again,
就得全部拆了重做了
You'd have to take the whole thing apart.
所以说 我要特别再三强调
Therefore... and I cannot stress this strongly enough...
绝对不要去按那按钮
Do not press the button.
他刚刚说了什么
What'd he just say?
好像什么按钮之类的
Something about a button.
我是鲍伯
This is bob.
哦 我知道了
Yeah. No, I got it.
我明白 好的 我们20分钟内就到你那
I got it. Okay. Yeah, we'll see you there in about 20 minutes.
对不起 亲爱的 接到一个灭害呼叫
Sorry, honey, it's an extermination call.
我们要在去泡温泉前先到那稍微停一下
We gotta make one little stop before we get to the spa.
不会吧
Really?
老婆 这可是313呼叫哎 黄色级别的
Honey, it's a 313... code yellow.
到底是什么
What's that?
小负鼠(会装死的小型有袋类哺乳动物)
Possum.
你就不能直接说"负鼠"吗
Wouldn't it be faster to just say "possum"?
好啊 你非要剥夺这种魔法的乐趣吗
Well, sure, you want to take all the magic out of it.
这是什么东西来着
What's this stuff called again?
报纸呗
Newspaper.
就是古时候人们用来看新闻的工具
It's how people in the olden days got their news.
喂 盖比和阿乔啊 你们俩听着
Uh, gabe, jo, listen up.
PJ和我要离开一会 我要15分钟后回来
So p.J. And I have to leave, but I'll be back in like 15 minutes.
也就是说你们要独自照看查莉了
That means you're gonna be alone with charlie.
现在她正在楼上睡觉 应该不会吵到你们
Now she's taking a nap upstairs. She probably won't bother you.
可是万一查莉有什么状况
But if you have any problems with charlie,
你就赶紧拨我的手机知道吗
just give me a call on my cell.
她刚才又说了啥
What'd she say?
好像什么查莉之类的
Something about charlie.
哎哟 PJ啊
Ow, p.J.!
哦 哎哟哟 PJ
Oh! Ow, p.J.!
咋啦 出什么事了
What? What's wrong?
我想我弄破了牙
I think I broke my tooth.
让我瞧瞧 哎哟
Let me see. Ew!
里面流了好多血
It's a bloody mess in there.
怎么还有籽粒呢
And there's seeds.
是哦 你能不能带我去看牙医啊
Yeah, well, can you take me to the dentist?
哈哈 好极了
Ha, so awesome.
为啥 因为我牙齿破了吗
What? That I broke my tooth?
不是的 因为我逃脱"妈妈和PJ"日了
No, that I got out of mommy-and-p.J. Day.
真妙
This is so cool.
我以前还没看过你怎么做抓虫子工作的
I've never seen you in action doing your bug-catching "thang."
听着 现在要抓的这东西
Okay, look, the "thang" that we're catching.
不是虫子 是负鼠
Is not a bug, it's a possum.
随便
Mm-hmm.
倒是和"惊讶"押韵的啦 砰
Which rhymes with awesome. Bam!
哎哟
Ow!
别闹了啦
Will you cut that out?
人家在工作呢 配合一下啦
I'm on duty. Thank you.
那好 这就开始
Okay. All right, here we go.
我觉得咱碰到个麻烦
I think we've got a problem.
那好 看来我只好下次再观赏你的虫子了
Oh well, guess I'll have to see you do your "thang" some other time.
走吧 我们享受按摩去
Come on. Let's go get massages.
还是等等
Um, or...
铛铛 来来来来来
Pop! Nah nah nah nah nah!
你不是吧
Oh no.
求你了 要我也会为你做的
Please? I would do this for you.
这绝对是咱的雷人约会亚军得主
Well, this is officially our second-worst date ever.
那最雷人的冠军是哪次
What was the worst?
跟你的爷爷奶奶一起泡澡
Hot tubbing with your grandparents.
你说的对 那次确实够呛
No, you're right. That was a bad idea.
哎哟
Ow ow.
借过 借过
Oh, excuse me, excuse me.
我妹妹得马上见牙医 她嘴里血流不止
Uh, my sister needs to see the dentist. Her mouth is all bloody.
情况很糟 嘴里都是籽儿
It's really bad. There's seeds.
姓什么
Last name?
姓邓肯的
Duncan.
哦 好的 找到你名字了
Oh okay. Yeah, we have you right here.
PJ·邓肯 约的是三点钟
P.J. Duncan, 3:00.
啥 可这不太对吧
What? But that-that can't be right.
你错了 找的就是你小子
No, that is right.
你好 PJ
Hello, P.J.
埃米特
Emmett?
你来干啥
What are you doing here?
是我叫他来的
I asked him to come.
你怎么不捂着嘴了
Why aren't you holding your mouth anymore?
因为今天不是我要来看牙医
Because I'm not seeing the dentist today.
是你去看
You are.
PJ 到时间了
P.J., it's time.
不要啊
No!
哎哟哟
Ow!
这我可做不来的
I can't do this.
不行
No!
你可以的 你是有心结没错
Yes, you can. Okay? You have a problem,
不过我们会帮你克服的
But we're gonna help you through it.
我们都是为了你最好打算的 兄弟
We all want what's best for you, man.
听着 不如我保证今后开始用牙线还不成吗
Look, what if I promise to start flossing?
你都不知保证过多少次了
Okay, we've heard those promises before.
加油啊 兄弟 坚强些
Come on, man, be strong.
你说的对
You're right.
不就是看个小牙么
It's just a little tooth.
就一颗小牙牙
乖小孩
Thattaboy.
不行 不行 不行
No no no!
抓住他 抓住他
Get him, get him!
PJ 别挣了 别闹了
P.J., let go! Let go, let go.
我们的初拥抱哎
Our first hug.
求你现在别恶心我了
Oh, not now!
别逼我刷你哦
Don't make me brush you!
哎呀 跑哪里去了
Oh no. Where are my...
我的眼镜啊
...Glasses?
晕 我的牙这回真的破了
Oh! Now my tooth is really broken.
哎哟
Oh!
PJ 跟我走吧
P.J., let's go.
我就说 ”还不如买个鱼缸放着“
I said, "let's get a fish tank."
医生偏说是 “没事啊 大牙刷肯定很给力”
He said, "no, the big toothbrush will be fun."
查莉 睡觉吧 求你别哭啦
Charlie, go to sleep, please. Just stop.
盖比 除非那娃子能涂色 不然快把她弄走
Gabe, unless that kid can paint, get her out of here.
泰迪 你到底啥时能回来啊
Teddy, when are you getting home?
我才不管你那蠢牙
I don't care about your stupid tooth.
你不能把查莉扔给我一人啊
You can't leave me alone with charlie.
别挂 泰迪 晕
Wait, teddy! Oh.
你不是一个人哦 盖比
You're not alone, Gabe.
我是不会帮你的啦 不过你不是一个人
I'm not gonna help you, but you're not alone.
这是啥味道
What's that smell?
肯定是那娃子拉屎拉尿了
It's coming from the business end of that kid.
你得赶紧帮她换
You gotta change it.
我不懂怎么换尿布啊
I don't know how to change a diaper.
不就跟分解一个墨西哥鸡肉卷 差不多么
It's just like taking apart a burrito.
拆完再塞回去
And then putting it back together.
我看我这辈子也甭想吃墨西哥卷了
I think I've eaten my last burrito.
你看起来真可爱呀
You look adorable.
闭嘴
Shut up.
好了 亲爱的 负鼠困在夹子上了
Okay, honey, look, the possum's in the trap.
你要做的只不过是进去给它绑上绳子
All you gotta do... you just gotta tie the rope to it.
然后我把它拉出来就行了
And I'll pull it right out.
造孽哟
OH
我爱你哦
I love you.
谁理你
Whatever.
菩萨喂
Oh my gosh.
亲爱的 你看到啥了
What do you see, honey?
尽是灰 蜘蛛网还有虫子
Dirt, cobwebs, bugs.
老公 真不晓得你怎么能整天都干这活
I don't know how you do this all day, Bob.
因为我知道家里有你在等我啊 老婆
That's 'cause I know I'm coming home to you, sweetie.
闭嘴吧你
Oh, shut up.
好了 我看到捕鼠夹了
Okay, I see the trap.
老公 我觉得这不像负鼠哎
Bob, I'm not so sure, this is a possum.
你是啥意思
What do you mean?
那个 负鼠是黑一道白一道的么
Well, are possums black with a white stripe?
啥 天 快出来 那不是负鼠 是
What? No, get out. That's not a possum. That's a...
是臭鼬啊
Skunk.
注：北美臭鼬 大小如猫 蓬松大尾 一日受喷 一月不退 本剧翻译深受其害过
啊呀呀 查莉 你别动好吗
Ah, charlie, stay still.
这该死的臭尿布
Stupid diapers.
你那边能消停点不
Can you please keep it down back there?
人家这儿正努力工作呢
I'm trying to work here.
好吧
Okay.
要知道 如果你能帮我 就会容易很多
You know, this would be a lot easier if you helped me.
是没错 可我们有协议的
Yes, it probably would, but we had an agreement.
我管这边的爆发 你管你那边的
I'll handle my thing that explodes and you'll handle yours.
那得了 我们有麻烦了
Well, we've got a problem.
我用光了所有的干净尿布
I'm all out of clean diapers.
现在该怎么办？
Now what am I gonna do?
好啦 小查莉 现在舒服了吧
Okay, Charlie, all better now.
那是件衬衫还有胶带纸吧
Is that a shirt... And duct tape?
系啲
Yes.
是么
Oh.
瞧 我管这叫 “新一代衬衫尿布”
See, I call it "the shirt diaper."
好就好在她的屁屁被完美呵护
The good thing is that she's protected.
而且那也不是我的衬衫
And it's not my shirt.
又咋啦
Oh, now what?
那小孩怎么就不能坐着不动呢
Why can't she just sit still?
我看除非是用更多胶布绑着她才动不了
I bet some more duct tape would make her sit still.
喂 我要练习之后的辩论赛
Hey, I'm gonna need to practice for my debate later.
你能帮我想个题目吗
Could you give me a topic?
行啊
Okay.
就这个好了 你为什么不能和我约会呢
How about, why won't you go out with me?
不行 我要的是正反方都能辩论的题目
No, I need a topic I can argue from both sides.
行啦 看好牙了
Okay, here we go.
我没做梦吗
Is this real life?
医生给他打了麻药
The doctor gave him some anesthesia.
泰迪 轮到你了
Teddy, come on back.
泰迪吗
Teddy?
我有个妹妹也叫泰迪
I have a sister named teddy.
好吧 你不喜欢胡萝卜是吧
Okay, so you didn't like carrots.
要不来点美味的蜜桃酱
How about some yummy peaches?
拿去吃吧
There you go.
哟
Oh!
够了 你是不知死活啊
That's it. You're in trouble now.
阿乔 过来
Jo, get in here!
你现在又想要干什么
What do you want now?
她不肯吃东西
She won't eat.
关我啥事
Not my problem.
喂
Hey!
我跟你说话时不许跑掉
Don't walk away when I'm talking to you.
我还有活要干
I have work to do.
我不管
I don't care.
我正经受非人折磨的一天
I'm having a really bad day.
我所要求的不过是一小点尊重
And all I'm asking for is a little respect.
那就是说我的工作就不重要吗
Oh, so what I do isn't important?
别歪曲我的话
Stop putting words into my mouth.
哼 我告诉你 姑娘受够了
You know what? That's it.
我要走了
I'm outta here.
你不能走
You can't leave.
你等着瞧啊
Oh yeah? Watch me.
阿乔 等等 别走
Jo, wait, don't go.
这是我第一次单独照看查莉
It's the first time I've been left alone with Charlie.
我搞的一团糟
I'm blowing it.
我自己一人实在是不来塞啊
I can't do this by myself.
好吧 我就帮你看看小孩
All right, I'll help you with the baby.
不过你先警告你
But just so you know,
我玩过的娃娃最后都以拧断脑袋告终的
every doll I've ever had ended up without its head.
瞧瞧你自己 你真的很会哄宝宝啊
Would you look at that? You're really good with babies.
没错 本姑娘超有才
Yeah, I guess I am.
但你要敢跟别人说 我就要你好看
If you ever tell anyone, I'll hurt you.
我们回来啦
We're back.
好了 来吧 小查莉 我们出去喽
Oh, here we go, charlie. Here you go.
我在夏威夷吗
Am I in hawaii...
跟奶奶一起来的吗
With grandma?
我告诉过你的 这是我奶奶的眼镜而已
I told you, these are my grandma's glasses.
总不能因为我戴着这眼镜就说我是老奶奶
Just because I'm wearing them doesn't make me grandma.
你脾气真不好 老奶奶
You're cranky, old lady.
埃米特喂 我姐呢
Hey, Emmett, where's teddy?
我们把她带到辩论赛现场就放下她了
Dropped her off at her debate.
好了 哥们 不如先坐下吧
Okay, buddy, how about we have a seat?
这玩意一路跟着我回家啊
This thing followed me all the way home.
好啊 孩子们
Hey kids.
嗨 老爸
Hey dad.
查莉怎么穿着衬衫当尿片呢
Why is charlie wearing a shirt diaper?
说来话长 老妈人呢
Uh, long story. Where's mom?
说来话更长
Longer story.
大家好啊
Hi, everybody.
妈妈我给熏到了
Mommy got stung.
都是你们老爸的错
It was all daddy's fault.
亲爱的 你能拿一下你身后的东西嘛
Uh, honey, can you get that thing behind you?
就在后面
Right back there.
爱你哦
Love you.
给我收声
Shut up.
老婆啊 你就仔仔细细
Honey, just scrub yourself real
用番茄汁给自己全身上下擦个2小时吧
good with that tomato juice for about two hours.
这样就可以消除那味道了 希望如此
It'll get the smell right out... I hope.
孩儿们 永远别跟着你老爸去泡桑拿
Kids, don't ever go to the spa with daddy.
呀呀呀
Hey hey hey.
我的小宝贝 爸爸跟你说呀
Hey, baby girl. I tell you what:
爸爸给你去换真的尿布 好不好
Let's get you a real diaper, okay?
载我的车子来了
Oh, that's my ride.
我饿死了
I'm starving.
你饿不饿呀
Are you hungry?
真不敢相信我要说的话
I can't believe I'm gonna say this,
不过我玩的挺开心的
But I had fun.
我也是
Me too.
而且我们还做完了一个很漂亮的工程
And we finished a pretty awesome project too.
就是 都等不及看那火山爆发的样子了
I know. Can't wait to see that volcano erupt.
我也是
I know.
那就看呗
Okay.
别 别 千万不要啊
No! No! Wait, don't don't don't!
火山轰隆轰隆啦
Volcano made a boom boom.
以下是我陈述的原因
And that is why.
为了学生们的安全
For the safety of our students.
以及免除家长们的担忧
And the peace of mind of our parents,
我将为手机在学校使用而辩论
I would argue that cell phone use in school.
不仅应该允许使用
Should not only be allowed,
而且更应该鼓励使用手机
It should be encouraged.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
邓肯小姐 反方辩词如何呢
Miss duncan, your rebuttal?
Ahem.
咳
秀鸡的喜用
Cellular phone usage.
系一个严肃的法题
Is a serious problem.
给众多消灰姐带来诸多疑问
That presents many challenges for the consumer.
说啥呃
What?
我是说
I said,
使用手机是一个重要议题
Cellular phone usage is a serious issue...
姐认输了
I concede.
嗨 小查莉 我是你盖比哥
Hey, charlie, gabe here.
今天我来录视频日记
And I'm doing the video diary tonight.
因为泰迪现在说话有困难
Because teddy's having some troubles with her words.
不是很大不了的
Nothing serious.
是哦
Yeah.
不管怎么说 今天都是我第一次照顾你
Anyway, today was the first day I took care of you.
非常圆满落幕
It went totally perfect.
瞎说
What?
好吧 是出了点小岔子
Okay, there were a few problems.
不过 要我说 你被照顾的很好哇
But, I mean, you're fine.
所以他们大概下次还会让我再来照看你的
So they're probably going to make me take care of you again.
祝你好运啰 查莉
Yeah. Good luck, charlie.
盖比 真得说这事虽然不是很确定对否
I've got to say, gabe, I wasn't sure about these things,
但这玩意儿还真舒服的很咧
But they are really comfortable.
是哦
Yeah.
我都不相信这下可以省多少事了
I can't believe how much time I'm
因为咱根本不用跑厕所
going to save by not having to go to the bathroom.
老兄 哈
Dude, ha!
人家现在正省着事呢 你懂我意思吧
I'm saving time right now, if you know what I mean.
给力哦
Nice.
喂 老爸 比赛开始了
Hey, dad, game's on.
呀呼
Yeah. Whoo!
挺潇洒的嘛 老爸
Looking good, dad.
哦哟 重要的是感觉潇洒 儿子
Oh, feelin' good, son.
呀呼 呀呼
Whoo! Whoo.